<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Attending and Volunteer Professors</title>
    <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty.html</link>
    <description>Volunteer and Attending Professors oversee teaching activities of the residents in the UCSF Orthodontic clinic.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In the resident practice, treatment is managed by a UCSF faculty member in concert with a postgraduate resident. Residents are licensed dentists who are in a three-year training program to become orthodontic specialists.  &lt;br/&gt;Your treatment plan is developed by your resident, together with an attending faculty member. At each visit you are seen by both the resident and faculty member. Visits can take longer, but fees in the residency program are lower than in the faculty clinic or at other private practices. </description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Steven W. Frank</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2015/12/15_Dr._Steven_W._Frank.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93eba561-ac35-48a5-bd85-4686cfd28b3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 14:02:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2015/12/15_Dr._Steven_W._Frank_files/Dr.%20Steven%20Frank.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Media/object003_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:182px; height:260px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Steven Frank is the Postgraduate Residency Program Director and a Clinical Professor for the Division of Orthodontics in the Department of Orofacial Sciences at the University of California, San Francisco (UCSF). Dr. Frank first attended the University of California, Berkeley where he earned a B.A. in Neurobiology. He subsequently went to Georgetown University, School of Dentistry, where he received a DDS. He then completed an orthodontic residency at Loma Linda University, Department of Orthodontics and earned a M.S. in Orthodontics. He is also a Diplomate of the American Board of Orthodontics. Dr. Frank came to UCSF after over 30 years of private practice and then transitioned into academic teaching, by initially joining the orthodontic faculty as part time instructor and then being appointed as the full time Orthodontic Postgraduate Program Director. Dr. Frank is passionate about teaching all aspects of orthodontics and dentofacial orthopedics, but likes to focus on early treatment, quality finishing of orthodontic cases, and advanced diagnosis and treatment planning.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2015/12/15_Dr._Steven_W._Frank_files/Dr.%20Steven%20Frank.jpg" length="33963" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Gerald Nelson</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2014/11/30_Dr._Gerald_Nelson.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44b5b0c2-71ba-4baf-9161-aa945249048f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 18:31:59 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2014/11/30_Dr._Gerald_Nelson_files/unknown.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Media/object007_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:182px; height:260px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Gerald Nelson graduated from the UC School of Dentistry in 1965 with a DDS and an Orthodontic Specialty Certificate. &lt;br/&gt;Jerry started with UCSF Division of Orthodontics as faculty in 1994, and has at times held the positions of Clinic Director, Vice Chair and Interim Chair of the Orthodontic Division. Presently he is full time clinical faculty.  In 1972, he and his private practice partner, Dr. Michael Meyer, co-founded an evening mixed dentition orthodontic clinic at La Clinica de la Raza in Oakland that continues and includes orthodontic residents.  For over 20 years, he held a post of Clinical Editor for the American Journal of Orthodontics, and Editor in Chief of the Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists Bulletin.  Collaboration with Korean Orthodontic University Programs has resulted in many publications on the use of temporary anchorage devices.  He has been listed as one of the top 100 authors for the American Journal of Orthodontics and Dental Orthopedics, and has reviewed over 100 articles for that publication. He has lectured on the use of 3D radiography for orthodontic treatment planning. He was honored with the opportunities to deliver the Alton Moore Lecture at the University of Washington in 2014, and the Mershon Lecture at the AAO Annual Session in San Francisco in 2015. Jerry and his wife, Pamela Grove, have six grown children and seven grandchildren.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2014/11/30_Dr._Gerald_Nelson_files/unknown.jpg" length="20917" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Ib Nielsen</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2013/12/1_Dr._Ib_Nielsen.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4586d29f-a0f3-4d4e-97d7-1f1e09471262</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 1 Dec 2013 12:22:20 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2013/12/1_Dr._Ib_Nielsen_files/droppedImage.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Media/object137_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:182px; height:259px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Dr. Nielsen is a Board Certified Orthodontist and a Clinical Professor (Emeritus) at the University of California, San Francisco. He received his dental education at the Royal Dental college of Århus, Denmark and his Orthodontic education at the Royal Dental College of Copenhagen, Denmark under Professor Arne Bjőrk (MSc). After graduation Dr. Nielsen continued as instructor at the Post Graduate Program of Orthodontics in Copenhagen until 1982 when he came to UCSF as Clinical Assistant Professor under Professor Dr. Robert Isaacson. He has remained at UCSF until the present as Clinical Professor and also holds a Certificate of Orthodontics from UCSF. In 1991 he opened a part-time private practice in Vacaville while still teaching half-time at UCSF. Dr. Nielsen has lectured worldwide, most recently in India, Iran and Taiwan and published more than 50 articles in orthodontic journals on normal and abnormal facial growth and many other topics including cephalometric analysis of growth and treatment, etiology and development of malocclusion, functional appliance treatment, muscle function and jaw movement in TMD patients and long-term stability of orthodontic treatment. Currently he is Director of Preceptorships and Fellowships in Orthodontics at UCSF and teaches part-time.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2013/12/1_Dr._Ib_Nielsen_files/droppedImage.png" length="34023" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Paul Kasrovi</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2011/11/30_Dr._Paul_Kasrovi.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8b67cf6-bb23-4a4c-a42f-dcc4932a3421</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 18:37:18 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2011/11/30_Dr._Paul_Kasrovi_files/unknown.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Media/object011_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:182px; height:260px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Dr. Paul Kasrovi completed his doctoral and postdoctoral education at UCSF, receiving both a specialty certificate in Orthodontics and a Master of Science degree in Oral Biology. Dr. Kasrovi is board certified by the American Board of Orthodontics. Before making a career change to dentistry, he had received a Bachelor of Science in Biomedical Engineering from USC and a Master of Science in Electrical Engineering from the University of Pennsylvania and worked as a systems engineer for AT&amp;amp;T Bell Laboratories.&lt;br/&gt;In addition to his commitment to the group practice, Dr. Kasrovi is a Clinical Professor at the UCSF School of Dentistry, division of Orthodontics where he has been teaching since 1995. He has also served as a Clinical Supervisor at the orthodontic teaching clinic at La Clinica de La Raza in Oakland.&lt;br/&gt;As an active member of the orthodontic and dental community, Dr. Kasrovi is affiliated with several professional associations. His affiliations include:&lt;br/&gt;	•	Presdent-Elect of the Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists&lt;br/&gt;	•	Past President and member of the California Association of Orthodontists&lt;br/&gt;	•	Director and member of the Northern CA. Edward H. Angle Society of Orthodontists&lt;br/&gt;	•	University advocate for the American Board of Orthodontics&lt;br/&gt;	•	Past President and member of the Berkeley Dental Society&lt;br/&gt;	•	Member of the American Dental Association&lt;br/&gt;	•	Member of the California Dental Association&lt;br/&gt;	•	Member of the American Association of Orthodontists&lt;br/&gt;	•	Member of the College of Diplomates of the American Board of Orthodontics&lt;br/&gt;	•	Member of the Peninsula Orthodontic Research Group&lt;br/&gt;	•	Member of Omicron Kappa Upsilon, a National Dental Honor Society&lt;br/&gt;Dr. Kasrovi is a published author of articles in the American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics, the Journal of the California Dental Association, and the Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists Bulletin. He has had his research presented at the meetings of the International Association of Dental Research and the American Society for Bone and Mineral Research. He has lectured on orthodontic care locally, nationally, and internationally.&lt;br/&gt;Dr. Kasrovi and his wife, Leila, have two children, Dara and Kiana. Dr. Kasrovi enjoys spending time with his family and is passionate about traveling, skiing, soccer, Bay Area sports teams, and playing bass guitar in a local East Bay band.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2011/11/30_Dr._Paul_Kasrovi_files/unknown.jpg" length="56796" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Nga Hoang</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2011/8/30_Dr._Nga_Hoang.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4899f8c3-61f9-497a-aaab-a94173c0a58e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 18:44:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2011/8/30_Dr._Nga_Hoang_files/DSC_7837-filtered.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Media/object012_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:182px; height:259px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Nga recognized that volunteer faculty members had a pivotal role in shaping her professionally. Thus, she is ecstatic to be able to give back her time to the Division of Orthodontics as Volunteer Assistant Clinical Professor, teaching the residents orthodontic literature review as well as preparing them for the ABO written exam. Outside of teaching and practicing orthodontics, Nga enjoys salsa-dancing, reading, and being one with the great outdoors.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2011/8/30_Dr._Nga_Hoang_files/DSC_7837-filtered.jpg" length="94591" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Fred Johnston</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2010/7/30_Dr._Fred_Johnston.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20663906-9376-4e35-9e45-b8ca98b1ca02</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 18:34:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2010/7/30_Dr._Fred_Johnston_files/CV.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Media/object010_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:182px; height:260px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Dr. Frederick Johnston was born in Mercedes,Texas a small town in South Texas. His mother was a single parent who raised 8 kids. Trying to survive ﬁnancially, he worked as a shoe shine boy, worked in the hot ﬁelds picking cotton, tomatoes, lettuce. Every spare moment after school hours, was spent working and contributing on making ends meet with the big family. He was certainly disadvantaged but his mother always stressed the importance of an education. Being a good athlete, he excelled in Football, Basketball, Track and ﬁeld and Baseball in high school. In college, Dr. Johnston received a track scholarship and in his sophomore year he won national champion in the High Hurdles. The following year he won the Lone Star conference hurdle award. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Following College, he was drafted into the US Army where he served as a medic, dental assistant, dental technician and dental hygienist. He continued to accelerate in sports in the Army. In the Army he received the outstanding trainee award, runner up leadership award and maximized the PT test of 500 points twice. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After the US ARMY, Dr. Johnston was accepted to UCLA School of Dentistry. He continued to compete in AAU track competition. At UCLA, he continued to train for the decathlon his junior and senior year.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After UCLA, UCSF accepted Dr. Johnston for the Orthodontic program where he received his certificate in Orthodontics. He has continued to compete in Masters Track and Field where he has won 3 world championship title in the High Hurdles. He has been a single parent raising his two great Kids, Mark and Rachel. At the present, he is the owner of Olympic Orthodontics in Dubln, California. Dr. Johnston has 38 years of experience practicing Orthodontics.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Attending_and_Volunteer_Faculty/Entries/2010/7/30_Dr._Fred_Johnston_files/CV.jpg" length="100678" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
