<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="A14B7412-57B6-441C-9931-FA62DA6B98C4">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160620" date="2016-06-20 23:29:04 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Dr. Solem&#x2019;s clinical focus ranges from simple aligner (Invisalign&#xAE;) treatments for dental crowding, to combined surgical&#x2013;orthodontic approaches for severe facial deformity. Previous to joining UCSF, he provided clinical orthodontic care at UCLA Ronald Regan Pediatric Hospital and Eisner Pediatric Medicine in Los Angeles. At these centers he treated individuals with rare craniofacial anomalies, pioneering new treatments which have been featured in major scientific publications. His training in this field includes an advanced fellowship in special needs and craniofacial anomalies at the University of Michigan. &#xD;&#xD;In addition to specialty procedures, Dr. Solem provides comprehensive treatment in traditional orthodontics, delivering care to patients from all backgrounds. Outside of the clinic, he enjoys spending time in the local mountains and beaches, surfing, running, and playing the cello and guitar.&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Selected Publications:&#xD;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	1.	Craniosynostosis and Rare Clefts,  The Treatment of Dentofacial Deformity in Craniosynostosis, Christensen, R., Moschik, C., Abedini, S., Wu, T., Solem, R.C.&#x2028;NOVA SCIENCE PUBLISHERS, INC.&#x2028;400 Oser Avenue, Suite 1600, Hauppauge, NY&#xD;	2.	Solem, R.C., Eames, B.F., Tokita, M., Schneider, R.A. 2011 Mesenchymal and mechanical mechanisms of secondary cartilage induction. Developmental Biology 356: 28-39.&#xD;	3.	Solem, R.C., Marasco, R., Gutierrez-Pulido, L., Kim, S-H, Nelson, G. Three-dimensional Soft and Hard Tissue Change in the Treatment of Bimaxillary Protrusion. American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics, 2013 Aug; 144 (2)&#xD;	4.	Solem, R.C. Limitation of a cross-sectional study. American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics, 2015 Aug; 148:205.&#xD;	5.	Solem, R.C., Martz, M., Weiss, E., Reese, P., Kawamoto, H., Lee, J. Multidisciplinary Treatment of Antley-Bixler Syndrome. The Cleft Palate-Craniofacial Journal, 2016 June.&#xD;	6.	Solem, R.C., Ruellas, A., Miller, A., Kelly, K., Ricks-Oddie, J., Cevidanes, L. Congenital and Acquired Mandibular Asymmetry: Mapping Growth in Three Dimensions. American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics, 2016 Aug.&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Dr. R Christian Solem&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Monday, June 20, 2016&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="20_Dr._R_Christian_Solem_files/shapeimage_4.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="224px" height="297px"/>
</content>
