<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Faculty</title>
    <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty</link>
    <description>The UCSF Orthodontics Faculty Clinic includes board-certified or board-eligible orthodontists with years of practice experience. All providers are UCSF faculty members. They are at the forefront of the orthodontics profession, publishing research and teaching the next generation of dentists and orthodontic specialists.

If time is an important factor for you, regular visits in faculty clinic are more efficient than in the residency program. The faculty clinic is most like a private orthodontic practice.

The list below includes Orthodontic Faculty Clinic Providers and other distinguished faculty in our division at UCSF.</description>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Steven W. Frank</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2015/12/15_Dr._Steven_W._Frank.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93eba561-ac35-48a5-bd85-4686cfd28b3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 14:02:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Steven Frank is the Postgraduate Residency Program Director and a Clinical Professor for the Division of Orthodontics in the Department of Orofacial Sciences at the University of California, San Francisco (UCSF). Dr. Frank first attended the University of California, Berkeley where he earned a B.A. in Neurobiology. He subsequently went to Georgetown University, School of Dentistry, where he received a DDS. He then completed an orthodontic residency at Loma Linda University, Department of Orthodontics and earned a M.S. in Orthodontics. He is also a Diplomate of the American Board of Orthodontics. Dr. Frank came to UCSF after over 30 years of private practice and then transitioned into academic teaching, by initially joining the orthodontic faculty as part time instructor and then being appointed as the full time Orthodontic Postgraduate Program Director. Dr. Frank is passionate about teaching all aspects of orthodontics and dentofacial orthopedics, but likes to focus on early treatment, quality finishing of orthodontic cases, and advanced diagnosis and treatment planning.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object003.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2015/12/15_Dr._Steven_W._Frank.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Gerald Nelson</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2014/11/30_Dr._Gerald_Nelson.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44b5b0c2-71ba-4baf-9161-aa945249048f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 18:31:59 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Gerald Nelson graduated from the UC School of Dentistry in 1965 with a DDS and an Orthodontic Specialty Certificate. &lt;br/&gt;Jerry started with UCSF Division of Orthodontics as faculty in 1994, and has at times held the positions of Clinic Director, Vice Chair and Interim Chair of the Orthodontic Division. Presently he is full time clinical faculty.  In 1972, he and his private practice partner, Dr. Michael Meyer, co-founded an evening mixed dentition orthodontic clinic at La Clinica de la Raza in Oakland that continues and includes orthodontic residents.  For over 20 years, he held a post of Clinical Editor for the American Journal of Orthodontics, and Editor in Chief of the Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists Bulletin.  Collaboration with Korean Orthodontic University Programs has resulted in many publications on the use of temporary anchorage devices.  He has been listed as one of the top 100 authors for the American Journal of Orthodontics and Dental Orthopedics, and has reviewed over 100 articles for that publication. He has lectured on the use of 3D radiography for orthodontic treatment planning. He was honored with the opportunities to deliver the Alton Moore Lecture at the University of Washington in 2014, and the Mershon Lecture at the AAO Annual Session in San Francisco in 2015.&#x2028;Jerry and his wife, Pamela Grove, have six grown children and seven grandchildren.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object007.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2014/11/30_Dr._Gerald_Nelson.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Ib Nielsen</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2013/12/1_Dr._Ib_Nielsen.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4586d29f-a0f3-4d4e-97d7-1f1e09471262</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 1 Dec 2013 12:22:20 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Dr. Nielsen is a Board Certified Orthodontist and a Clinical Professor (Emeritus) at the University of California, San Francisco. He received his dental education at the Royal Dental college of &#xC5;rhus, Denmark and his Orthodontic education at the Royal Dental College of Copenhagen, Denmark under Professor Arne Bj&#x151;rk (MSc). After graduation Dr. Nielsen continued as instructor at the Post Graduate Program of Orthodontics in Copenhagen until 1982 when he came to UCSF as Clinical Assistant Professor under Professor Dr. Robert Isaacson. He has remained at UCSF until the present as Clinical Professor and also holds a Certificate of Orthodontics from UCSF. In 1991 he opened a part-time private practice in Vacaville while still teaching half-time at UCSF. Dr. Nielsen has lectured worldwide, most recently in India, Iran and Taiwan and published more than 50 articles in orthodontic journals on normal and abnormal facial growth and many other topics including cephalometric analysis of growth and treatment, etiology and development of malocclusion, functional appliance treatment, muscle function and jaw movement in TMD patients and long-term stability of orthodontic treatment. Currently he is Director of Preceptorships and Fellowships in Orthodontics at UCSF and teaches part-time.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object137.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2013/12/1_Dr._Ib_Nielsen.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Sneha Oberoi</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2013/9/30_Dr._Sneha_Oberoi.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62a7f969-4467-4c94-b281-70c81752639b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 18:33:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Dr. Snehlata (Sneha) Oberoi, BDS, DDS, MDS, a board certified orthodontist, &#xA0;is the Director of the Cleft and Craniofacial Orthodontic Program and a Professor of Clinical Orofacial Sciences at the UCSF School of Dentistry. She completed her craniofacial orthodontic fellowship at UCSF in 2004, after receiving her dental and orthodontic training from India in 1994. She completed her certificate in Orthodontics from UCSF in 2014. She is the craniofacial orthodontist on the UCSF Craniofacial Team, where she provides assessment and treatment recommendations for children with cleft lip and palate and other craniofacial anomalies. She maintains a robust orthodontic faculty practice in the UCSF Orthodontic Clinic and is the attending for craniofacial patients treated by the residents. She provides teaching and supervision of orthodontic and pediatric dentistry residents and dental students on rotation in the Center for Craniofacial Anomalies. Dr. Oberoi has published over 50 articles in peer reviewed journals, as well as four book chapters. She serves as a reviewer for the Cleft Palate-Craniofacial Journal, the International Journal of Paediatric Dentistry, the Angle Orthodontist and the AJO-DO. Her research focuses on developing new methods to assess treatment outcomes for cleft lip and cleft palate and other craniofacial anomalies. She collaborates with the Center's medical geneticists to identify genetic mutations affecting orofacial defects. She lectures nationally and internationally. Dr. Oberoi is a member of the American Cleft Palate-Craniofacial Association, the American Association of Orthodontists, the Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists, California Association of Orthodontists and the Indian Orthodontic Society.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object008.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2013/9/30_Dr._Sneha_Oberoi.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Kjeld Aamodt</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2012/11/30_Dr._Kjeld_Aamodt.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9200ef97-6241-4e6d-b217-722291c273ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 18:47:23 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Dr. Aamodt&#x2019;s Faculty Practice focus&#x2019; on Invisalign, clear braces, and&#xA0;accelerated tooth straightening treatments. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;He was&#xA0;recently quoted for the Wall Street Journal article on Adult Orthodontics. &#x201C;Orthodontics combines health care with art,&#x201D; Kjeld says. &#x201C;Our patients&#x2019; faces are&#xA0;our canvases, and those smiles are showcased every day and have meaning for everything our patients do.&#x201D;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dr. Aamodt attended UCSF School of Dentistry, he completed a residency in the UCSF Division of Orthodontics.&#xA0;Dr. Aamodt has been involved in orthodontic research for several years,&#xA0;with a focus on understanding how the burden of malocclusion is distributed worldwide and how this has changed during the course of history, with a particular interest in why malocclusion develops. As a resident, Dr. Aamodt helped to build a network of universities in Central and South America to study how malocclusion and tooth decay may affect quality of life for indigenous groups.&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Kjeld Aamodt surfs and scuba dives, speaks Spanish, plays jazz guitar and bass, and recently got his private pilot&#x2019;s license. </description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object014.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2012/11/30_Dr._Kjeld_Aamodt.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Ophir Klein</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2012/10/30_Dr._Ophir_Klein.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6dbe7dd1-51fa-487c-a7dd-66457c236ae3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 18:28:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Ophir Klein is the Larry L. Hillblom Distinguished Professor in Craniofacial Anomalies, Professor of Orofacial Sciences and Pediatrics, and Chair of the Divisions of Craniofacial Anomalies and Orthodontics at the University of California, San Francisco (UCSF). He is also the Medical Director of the UCSF Craniofacial Center and Director of the UCSF Program in Craniofacial Biology. Dr. Klein was educated at the University of California, Berkeley, where he earned a B.A. in Spanish Literature. He subsequently attended Yale University School of Medicine, where he received a Ph.D. in Genetics and an M.D.. He then completed residencies at Yale-New Haven Hospital in Pediatrics and at UCSF in Clinical Genetics. Work in Dr. Klein&#x2019;s research group centers on organ development and regeneration, with a major focus on understanding the processes underlying craniofacial development and integrating evolutionary and developmental approaches.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object001.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2012/10/30_Dr._Ophir_Klein.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Art Miller</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2012/8/30_Dr._Art_Miller.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b82bbd1d-3441-4632-91eb-c64b7abc3fd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 18:33:54 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>My original research in the neuorphysiological parameters underlying the brain stem reflex of swallowing established a life long interest.   This work started as a thesis while a trainee of the Brain Research Institute at UCLA in 1970, led to several papers, a review in Physiological Reviews in 1982, a book on the Neurophysiological Principles Underlying Swallowing and Dysphagia in 1999, and the cooperation with several investigators at Johns Hopkins and the Medical College of Wisconsin in the development of a new society, the Dysphagia Research Society.  I have been on the executive board for several years and was President in 2007-2008 organizing our annual meeting which took place in Vancouver.   This annual meeting provides the basis for international investigators around the world to come and present their research.  Part of our function has been to expand our ties with investigators in Europe and Japan to develop more research presentations and joint meetings.  This has involved working with several groups in Europe and Japan to bring our different research groups closer together and has involved more traveling to German and Japan.   Many of the new concepts on rehabilitation in dysphagia are using principles established in neuroscience including electrical stimulation and transmagnetic cortical stimulation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;My interest in the brain stem and the neuromuscular system led to my research expanding to the craniomandibular region and its muscles, which brought me to UCSF over 40 years ago in 1975.  This interest in the craniofacial region has focused on the jaw muscles and their interaction with bone.  This has led to 15 years of research using the rhesus monkey as well as interacting with clinicians and researchers in craniofacial anomalies, temporomandibular disorders, and other dental fields. This work included publishing a book entitled:  Craniomandibular Muscles:  Their Role in Function and Form.  CRC Press, Boca Raton, Florida, 1991.  Some of this reserach has been with a good friend and colleague, Dr. Kuotaro Maki, from Showa University in Tokyo, in which we have worked for over 20 years together. This has been a long-term interaction which culminated in expanding our original studies using CT to evaluate cortical bone mineralization, to bringing a new system to USCF using volumetric three-dimensional analysis with cone beam computed tomography (CBCT).   We were the first institution in the United States to use a CBCT system, and we have developed a variety of joint projects that incorporate our orthodontic residents.   The cone beam CT system at UCSF has now become the standard for our Division of Orthodontics.   I also serve as the Director of the Oral and Craniofacial Sciences Master&#x2019;s Degree program complementing my work in the Division of Orthodontics.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some of the recent publications include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Chiang C, Jeffres M, Miller AJ, Hatcher, DC.  Three-dimensional airway evaluation in 387 subjects from one university orthodontic clinic using cone beam computed tomography.  Angle Orthodontics 82: 985-992, 2012.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Schlicher W, Nielsen, I, Huang JC, Maki K, Hatcher DC, Miller AJ Consistency and precision in landmark identification in three dimensional cone beam computed tomography scans. European Journal of Orthodontics 34:263-275, 2012&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;George JR, Chung S, Nielsen I, Goldberg AN, Miller AJ, Kezirian EJ.  Comparison of drug-induced sleep endoscopy and lateral cephalometry in obstructive sleep apnea.  Laryngoscope 122: 2600-2605, 2012&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Bailey E, Nelson G, Miller AJ, Andrews L, Johnson E.  Predicting tooth-size discrepancy:  A new formula utilizing revised landmarks and three-dimensional laser scanning technology.  American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics  143: 574-585, 2013&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shibazaki-Yorozuya R, Yamada A, Nagata S, Ueda K, Miller AJ, Maki K.  Three-dimensional longitudintal changes in craniofacial growth in untreated hemifacial microsomia patients using conebeam computed tomoraphy (CBCT)..  American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics May;145(5):579-94, 2014     &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Yao W, Bekmezian S, Hardy D, Kushner HW, Miller AJ, Huang JC, Lee JS.   &lt;a href="http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/25488314"&gt;Cone-beam computed tomographic comparison of surgically assisted rapid palatal expansion and multipiece Le Fort I osteotomy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;J Oral Maxillofac Surg. Mar;73(3):499-508. doi: 10.1016/j.joms.2014.08.024. Epub  2015    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ikeda R, Oberoi S, Wiley D, Woodhouse C, Tallman M, Tun W W, McNeill, C, Miller, AJ, Hatcher, D.  A novel three-dimensional analysis to evaluate temporomandibular joint space and shape.  American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics, March, 2016&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA0;Chang, MK, Sears, C, Huang JC, Miller AJ, Kushner HW, Lee, J   Correlation of airway volume with orthognathic surgical movement using cone-beam CT.  &#xA0;Journal of Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery, 2016&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some Recent Honors:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object009.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2012/8/30_Dr._Art_Miller.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Paul Kasrovi</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2011/11/30_Dr._Paul_Kasrovi.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8b67cf6-bb23-4a4c-a42f-dcc4932a3421</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 18:37:18 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Dr. Paul Kasrovi completed his doctoral and postdoctoral education at UCSF, receiving both a specialty certificate in Orthodontics and a Master of Science degree in Oral Biology. Dr. Kasrovi is board certified by the American Board of Orthodontics. Before making a career change to dentistry, he had received a Bachelor of Science in Biomedical Engineering from USC and a Master of Science in Electrical Engineering from the University of Pennsylvania and worked as a systems engineer for AT&amp;amp;T Bell Laboratories.&lt;br/&gt;In addition to his commitment to the group practice, Dr. Kasrovi is a Clinical Professor at the UCSF School of Dentistry, division of Orthodontics where he has been teaching since 1995. He has also served as a Clinical Supervisor at the orthodontic teaching clinic at La Clinica de La Raza in Oakland.&lt;br/&gt;As an active member of the orthodontic and dental community, Dr. Kasrovi is affiliated with several professional associations. His affiliations include:&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	Presdent-Elect&#xA0;of the Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	Past President and member of the California Association of Orthodontists&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	Director and member of the Northern CA. Edward H. Angle Society of Orthodontists&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	University advocate for the American Board of Orthodontics&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	Past President and member of the Berkeley Dental Society&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	Member of the American Dental Association&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	Member of the California Dental Association&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	Member of the American Association of Orthodontists&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	Member of the College of Diplomates of the American Board of Orthodontics&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	Member of the Peninsula Orthodontic Research Group&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	Member of Omicron Kappa Upsilon, a National Dental Honor Society&lt;br/&gt;Dr. Kasrovi is a published author of articles in the American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics, the Journal of the California Dental Association, and the Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists Bulletin. He has had his research presented at the meetings of the International Association of Dental Research&#xA0;and the American Society for Bone and Mineral Research. He has lectured on orthodontic care&#xA0;locally, nationally, and internationally.&lt;br/&gt;Dr. Kasrovi and his wife, Leila, have two children, Dara and Kiana. Dr. Kasrovi enjoys spending time with his family and is passionate about traveling, skiing, soccer, Bay Area sports teams, and playing bass guitar in a local East Bay band.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object011.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2011/11/30_Dr._Paul_Kasrovi.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Nga Hoang</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2011/8/30_Dr._Nga_Hoang.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4899f8c3-61f9-497a-aaab-a94173c0a58e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 18:44:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Nga recognized that volunteer faculty members had a pivotal role in shaping her professionally. Thus, she is ecstatic to be able to give back her time to the Division of Orthodontics as Volunteer Assistant Clinical Professor, teaching the residents orthodontic literature review as well as preparing them for the ABO written exam. Outside of teaching and practicing orthodontics, Nga enjoys salsa-dancing, reading, and being one with the great outdoors.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object012.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2011/8/30_Dr._Nga_Hoang.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Fred Johnston</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2010/7/30_Dr._Fred_Johnston.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20663906-9376-4e35-9e45-b8ca98b1ca02</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 18:34:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Dr. Frederick Johnston was born in Mercedes,Texas a small town in South Texas. His mother was a single parent who raised 8 kids. Trying to survive &#xFB01;nancially, he worked as a shoe shine boy, worked in the hot &#xFB01;elds picking cotton, tomatoes, lettuce. Every spare moment after school hours, was spent working and contributing on making ends meet with the big family. He was certainly disadvantaged but his mother always stressed the importance of an education. Being a good athlete, he excelled in Football, Basketball, Track and &#xFB01;eld and Baseball in high school. In college, Dr. Johnston received a track scholarship and in his sophomore year he won national champion in the High Hurdles. The following year he won the Lone Star conference hurdle award. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Following College, he was drafted into the US Army where he served as a medic, dental assistant, dental technician and dental hygienist. He continued to accelerate in sports in the Army. In the Army he received the outstanding trainee award, runner up leadership award and maximized the PT test of 500 points twice. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After the US ARMY, Dr. Johnston was accepted to UCLA School of Dentistry. He continued to compete in AAU track competition. At UCLA, he continued to train for the decathlon his junior and senior year.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After UCLA, UCSF accepted Dr. Johnston for the Orthodontic program where he received his certificate in Orthodontics. He has continued to compete in Masters Track and Field where he has won 3 world championship title in the High Hurdles. He has been a single parent raising his two great Kids, Mark and Rachel. At the present, he is the owner of Olympic Orthodontics in Dubln, California. Dr. Johnston has 38 years of experience practicing Orthodontics.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object010.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty/Entries/2010/7/30_Dr._Fred_Johnston.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>MMMM d, y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>10</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
