<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="1E08F395-AD12-4A7E-93BD-F04EF0C6B859">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160729" date="2016-07-29 16:11:55 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Orthodontic Residency</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;MISSION&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;The mission of the UCSF Postgraduate Program in Orthodontics is to contribute to the orthodontic specialty, orthodontic academic programs, orthodontic research, and the public by graduating broadly educated and well-trained clinician scientists.  An important ancillary mission of the educational process is to deliver quality orthodontic care for UCSF clinic patients.&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;PROGRAM DESCRIPTION &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;This is a full time program, requiring 36 months in active residence beginning July 1 each year. It is designed to prepare future leaders in the specialty of orthodontics, qualified for academic careers as well as for clinical practice. &#xD;&#xD;The program combines a foundation in basic sciences with clinical and behavioral training relevant to the delivery of orthodontic treatment.  Residents perform orthodontic care for the prevention and correction of malocclusions and facial disproportions.  The patient population includes children and adults. We emphasize a good knowledge base of maxillofacial structures and the function of the neuromuscular system.  The facility is modern.  Residents learn to operate a CBCT unit and to evaluate the scans. &#xD;&#xD;Instruction includes lectures, seminars, demonstrations, laboratory experience and conferences.  These experiences are coordinate with the clinical treatment of patients. &#xD;&#xD;Residents learn clinical skills while working in a team consisting of a first-, second-, and third-year resident and a full-time, highly skilled registered dental assistant.  Attending faculty is present for every patient visit. We teach orthodontic care with a variety of fixed and removable appliances.  All dental specialties are adjacent to the orthodontic clinic, facilitating interdisciplinary opportunities with oral and maxillofacial surgeons, periodontists, pediatric dentists, prosthodontists, and TMD specialists. Consultation with all medical specialists is also available on campus.  In the area of craniofacial anomalies, residents develop skills to evaluate the etiology, diagnosis, and prognosis of such patients.  Residents perform orthodontic treatment for patients with craniofacial anomalies and have a rotation in an active craniofacial diagnostic team. &#xD;&#xD;The certificate program is combined with the postgraduate academic program in Oral and Craniofacial Sciences, leading to the M.S. degree within the 3-year residency.  Residents complete a research project under the supervision of a faculty mentor.  We also offer a combined PhD-certificate program, which can be selected for those residents who are interested in pursuing an academic career. There is support available for the PhD portion (3-5 years) from the Oral and Craniofacial Sciences Program. </richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Updated December 20, 2015</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="20_Orthodontic_Residency_files/shapeimage_4.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="400px" height="300px"/>
</content>
