<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Current Residents</title>
    <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Current_Residents.html</link>
    <description>In the resident practice, treatment is managed by a UCSF faculty member in concert with a postgraduate resident. Residents are licensed dentists who are in a three-year training program to become orthodontic specialists.  &lt;br/&gt;Your treatment plan is developed by your resident, together with an attending faculty member. At each visit you are seen by both the resident and faculty member. Visits can take longer, but fees in the residency program are lower than in the faculty clinic or at other private practices. &lt;br/&gt;</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Christian Hagge</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2016/5/10_Dr._Christian_Hagge.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b358d2d5-4138-423e-a79f-89c2eaf4902e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 20:15:39 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2016/5/10_Dr._Christian_Hagge_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Media/object000_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:182px; height:250px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Eric grew up in Illinois, where he received his DMD degree from Southern Illinois University - School of Dental Medicine. In addition to studying orthodontics at UCSF he is collaborating to develop a Bluetooth enabled &amp;quot;SmartByte&amp;quot; retainer that can be synced to a mobile app. He hopes his work  will greatly improve orthodontic compliance and long term outcomes after braces. In his free time he enjoys golfing, exploring The City and everything outdoors!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2016/5/10_Dr._Christian_Hagge_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="15448" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Stephanie Purnomo</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Stephanie_Purnomo.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ffe0c85-9d9b-43b9-9072-37503b8fb501</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 08:47:09 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Stephanie_Purnomo_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Media/object001_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:182px; height:250px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Stephanie Purnomo is an outdoor enthusiast. She enjoys camping and recently hiked her way up Yosemite’s half dome. She is also a self-proclaimed expert garage sale hunter and collects succulents for fun. A bay area native, she attended UCSF for dental school and now residency. Her favorite part of ortho is talking to her patients and watching them smile bigger and brighter at each visit. &lt;br/&gt;“Orthodontics is fun and complex- it’s a lot like solving a puzzle that is constantly in motion,” she says. “Our job is to make teeth fit together properly, but the spectacular side effect is that we create beautiful smiles too!  “</description>
      <enclosure url="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Stephanie_Purnomo_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="11846" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Andrew Jheon</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Andrew_Jheon.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b61e7eca-d88e-4efe-bfdd-578fb1ff005f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 08:46:26 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Andrew_Jheon_files/unknown.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Media/object005_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:182px; height:250px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;I am an Assistant Professor in Residence in the Division of Craniofacial Anomalies, Department of Orofacial Sciences at UCSF. My interests lie in basic research, specifically in the molecular and cellular mechanisms of tooth development, renewal, and movement. In my laboratory, we utilize genetically modified mouse models to gain further understanding of the functional roles of genes and signaling pathways. The ultimate goal is to innovate or improve upon current preventive, diagnostic, and therapeutic methods in dentistry by translating biological data from basic research for application into the clinic. Concomitant to my research, I am a part-time Orthodontic resident and plan to be certified by the American Board of Orthodontics in 2017. </description>
      <enclosure url="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Andrew_Jheon_files/unknown.jpg" length="73323" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Wint Wint Tun</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Wint_Wint_Tun.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2b3b531-459f-4fcc-aedb-45f31aa91cc0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 08:45:20 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Wint_Wint_Tun_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Media/object002_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:182px; height:250px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Wint was born and raised in Myanmar (formally known as Burma). She grew up in a big family and is the youngest of five children. She received her bachelor of dental surgery in 2007 in Myanmar. After practicing general dentistry for a few years, she immigrated to US in 2009. She then went to UCSF International Dentist Program and received D.D.S. She is currently a second year orthodontic resident at UCSF. In her free time, Wint enjoys traveling, joining Zumba Class, spending time with her husband, cooking Burmese food and trying different cuisines. </description>
      <enclosure url="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Wint_Wint_Tun_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="12109" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Eric Castle</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Eric_Castle.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5508ecbe-c918-463d-801c-ee83d4a02da5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 08:42:25 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Eric_Castle_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Media/object003_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:182px; height:250px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Eric grew up in Illinois, where he received his DMD degree from Southern Illinois University - School of Dental Medicine. In addition to studying orthodontics at UCSF he is collaborating to develop a Bluetooth enabled &amp;quot;SmartByte&amp;quot; retainer that can be synced to a mobile app. He hopes his work  will greatly improve orthodontic compliance and long term outcomes after braces. In his free time he enjoys golfing, exploring The City and everything outdoors!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/30_Dr._Eric_Castle_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="12301" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Andrew Alexander</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/25_Dr._Andrew_Alexander.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4635e96-838a-4d23-bd5a-675b48cf4e8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 19:11:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Drew Alexander enjoys traveling to exotic places, the beach, snowboarding, hiking the awesome bay area trails, attending live sporting events, and pigging out on the amazing cuisine the city of San Francisco has to offer!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Born and raised in San Diego, stayed local for my undergraduate studies at UCSD, and then ventured out of the SoCal nest for an east coast experience where I attended Temple University school of dentistry.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“The change that orthodontics is able to create in terms of a person’s self confidence, appearance, and function are some of the things that I think make this profession awesome!”   </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Sara Adabi</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/25_Dr._Sara_Adabi.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f2380d8-3963-4dc3-a71e-f0a62b33ac12</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 19:10:10 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Sara Adabi is a first year orthodontic resident at UCSF. She earned her Bachelors of Science degree in Chemistry from UC Irvine and her Doctor of Dental Surgery degree from UCSF. After graduating from UCSF dental school in 2014, she spent a year doing an orthodontic research fellowship at University of Connecticut Health Center, where she published two papers in peer-reviewed journals and her love for orthodontics was solidified. Sara was born and raised in Iran but has made California her home, and couldn’t be happier to be back! In her free time she enjoys spending time with family and friends, trying new restaurants in the city, and traveling. She was involved in craniofacial research throughout dental school and is excited to continue studying with her mentor Dr. Sneha Oberoi. She hopes to treat craniofacial patients throughout her career and believes orthodontic treatment has the ability to transform people’s smiles and subsequently their lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Isaac Chen</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/25_Dr._Isaac_Chen.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d6845dc-6fb3-4f26-949f-ccce6bd5bd1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 19:09:01 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Isaac Chen, an Argentinian-Asian-American, loves eating Argentinian empanadas, Chinese dim sum and American BBQ. He speaks Spanish, Chinese and Taiwanese, enjoys weekends watching action movies and spending quality time with friends and family. With his diverse culture and multilingual capabilities, he treats his patients with personable and customized patient centered care. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As a resident at UCSF, he studies orthodontics and craniofacial anomalies, treats patients and conducts research. Isaac’s research focuses on sequencing supragingival dental plaque responsible for WSLs during fixed appliance orthodontic treatment. His goal is to advance the understanding of the microbial species involved in the etiology of WSLs and lead to the development of specific, targeted antimicrobial approaches to inhibit WSLs during orthodontic therapy. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Alan Wang</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/25_Dr._Alan_Wang.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b957cf6-3622-426c-9859-b2b287165bb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 19:05:37 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Allan grew up in Weston, Massachusetts.  He received his B.S. degree in Psychology from Tufts University in 2010 and his D.M.D. degree from the University of Pennsylvania in 2015.  He comes from a large dental family - his grandfather worked in the Dental Department of Chengdu Hospital, his mother is a practicing general dentist, his cousin is currently a 3rd year dental student, and his brother is in the process of applying to dental schools.  From assisting at his mother’s dental practice, Allan fell in love with the field from an early age.  He feels privileged to have been selected to UCSF’s Postgraduate Orthodontics Residency Class of 2018.  In his free time, Allan enjoys playing sports, reading, hiking and traveling.  Finally, he is an avid New England Patriots fan!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Alice Goodwin</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/25_Dr._Alice_Goodwin.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18d79b1e-860a-44bc-a99a-e593d46df0d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 19:04:57 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Alice Goodwin is a 3rd year resident and lives in San Francisco and likes to cook, run and hike all over the Bay Area. Since dental school, she has been interested in both treating patients and doing research in the lab. She completed dental school and a PhD at UCSF, studying how teeth develop and in particular how enamel, the hard outer covering of the teeth, forms. With her interest in craniofacial biology, she learned more about the exciting world of orthodontics, and she is now treating patients in the UCSF Orthodontic Clinic, learning to create beautiful and functional smiles. She plans to pursue an academic career to both treat patients and learn basic biology in the lab that may improve patient care in the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Cassandra Campbell</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/25_Dr._Cassandra_Campbell.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0119a00a-8f20-455c-9385-31f9ba79a793</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 19:03:56 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Cassandra Campbell is a first year orthodontic resident at UCSF and graduated dental school from University of Michigan, Go Blue! She grew up in Redding, California and received her B.S. in Molecular, Cellular and Developmental Biology from UC Santa Cruz in 2011. In her free time she enjoys playing soccer, training for her next half marathon, painting, or just taking it easy with a cup of coffee and a good book. She is currently learning how to play the guitar so she can jam with her talented father when she visits him in Redding. Throughout dental school her research focused on pharmaceutical interventions for premature fusion of cranial sutures, and she is excited to continue studying craniofacial anomalies and treating patients of a diverse background. Every day she looks forward to a helping her patients feel confident and communicating that to the world with a beautiful smile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Elizabeth Eve</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/25_Dr._Elizabeth_Eve.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1bedcb6-66a9-4304-825d-6a8b099b8a3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 19:03:08 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Elizabeth Eve is a Bay Area native who loves San Francisco's abundance of parks and hiking trails. She completed her undergraduate and dental training at Harvard University, where her professional interests included dental education and public health. Elizabeth enjoys the interdisciplinary nature of orthodontic care and tailoring her treatment approach to obtain the functional and esthetic goals of her patients. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Paiyal Popat</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2015/11/25_Dr._Paiyal_Popat.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7387bd0-8556-47d2-9829-09b1b6965d42</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 19:02:18 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Paiyal Popat grew up in Orlando, Florida where she studied micro/molecular biology at the University of Central Florida. Here was where she discovered her passion for dentistry and made the big move to Boston, Massachusetts to attend the Harvard School of Dental Medicine (HSDM) to receive her dental degree. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At HSDM, Paiyal had the opportunity to treat a variety of patients, assist orthodontic faculty, and conduct research on assessing access to oral health care for individuals with special needs and for individuals who are homeless. Additionally, Paiyal was able to continue her hobby of choreography and dance at HSDM. There she saw how mapping formations, planning smooth transitions, ensuring that there is appropriate time for each movement, and lastly, perfecting the fine details are the core principles that are shared in both choreography and the practice of orthodontics.&lt;br/&gt;At the innovative orthodontic program of UCSF, Paiyal plans to hone her skills as an orthodontist while expanding her interest in public health through research focused on the influence of diet on skeletal and dental malocclusion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Amir &#13;Dadgar- Yeganeh</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Residents/Entries/2013/6/15_Dr._Nga_Hoang.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e38a34e2-250b-49c3-a643-eacd4b87866f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 11:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Amir Dadgar-Yeganeh was born and raised in Iran until he was almost 15 years old. He then immigrated to the U.S. and started living in Los Angeles with his family.  He did his undergraduate study at UCLA and Dental school at UCSF. He was then accepted to the UCSF Orthodontic program and is currently a 3rd year orthodontic resident. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
