<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Faculty Clinic</title>
    <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty_Clinic</link>
    <description>Schedule a Free 
ConsultationThe UCSF Orthodontics Faculty Clinic includes board-certified or board-eligible orthodontists with years of practice experience. All providers are UCSF faculty members. They are at the forefront of the orthodontics profession, publishing research and teaching the next generation of dentists and orthodontic specialists.

If time is an important factor for you, regular visits in faculty clinic are more efficient than in the residency program. The faculty clinic is most like a private orthodontic practice.

The list below includes Orthodontic Faculty Clinic Providers and other distinguished faculty in our division at UCSF.</description>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. R Christian Solem</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty_Clinic/Entries/2016/6/20_Dr._R_Christian_Solem.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8c0c740-414f-4e1d-8130-05c137a56020</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 16:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Dr. Solem&#x2019;s clinical focus ranges from simple aligner (Invisalign&#xAE;) treatments for dental crowding, to combined surgical&#x2013;orthodontic approaches for severe facial deformity. Previous to joining UCSF, he provided clinical orthodontic care at UCLA Ronald Regan Pediatric Hospital and Eisner Pediatric Medicine in Los Angeles. At these centers he treated individuals with rare craniofacial anomalies, pioneering new treatments which have been featured in major scientific publications. His training in this field includes an advanced fellowship in special needs and craniofacial anomalies at the University of Michigan. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In addition to specialty procedures, Dr. Solem provides comprehensive treatment in traditional orthodontics, delivering care to patients from all backgrounds. Outside of the clinic, he enjoys spending time in the local mountains and beaches, surfing, running, and playing the cello and guitar.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Selected Publications:&lt;br/&gt;	1.	Craniosynostosis and Rare Clefts,  The Treatment of Dentofacial Deformity in Craniosynostosis, Christensen, R., Moschik, C., Abedini, S., Wu, T., Solem, R.C.&#x2028;NOVA SCIENCE PUBLISHERS, INC.&#x2028;400 Oser Avenue, Suite 1600, Hauppauge, NY&lt;br/&gt;	2.	Solem, R.C., Eames, B.F., Tokita, M., Schneider, R.A. 2011 Mesenchymal and mechanical mechanisms of secondary cartilage induction. Developmental Biology 356: 28-39.&lt;br/&gt;	3.	Solem, R.C., Marasco, R., Gutierrez-Pulido, L., Kim, S-H, Nelson, G. Three-dimensional Soft and Hard Tissue Change in the Treatment of Bimaxillary Protrusion. American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics, 2013 Aug; 144 (2)&lt;br/&gt;	4.	Solem, R.C. Limitation of a cross-sectional study. American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics, 2015 Aug; 148:205.&lt;br/&gt;	5.	Solem, R.C., Martz, M., Weiss, E., Reese, P., Kawamoto, H., Lee, J. Multidisciplinary Treatment of Antley-Bixler Syndrome. The Cleft Palate-Craniofacial Journal, 2016 June.&lt;br/&gt;	6.	Solem, R.C., Ruellas, A., Miller, A., Kelly, K., Ricks-Oddie, J., Cevidanes, L. Congenital and Acquired Mandibular Asymmetry: Mapping Growth in Three Dimensions. American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics, 2016 Aug.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object004.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty_Clinic/Entries/2016/6/20_Dr._R_Christian_Solem.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Kjeld Aamodt</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty_Clinic/Entries/2016/2/3_Dr._Kjeld_Aamodt.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8d46d07-289e-4f0d-b32a-1ba97fef15e7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 3 Feb 2016 12:55:15 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Dr. Aamodt&#x2019;s Faculty Practice focus&#x2019; on Invisalign, clear braces, and&#xA0;accelerated tooth straightening treatments. &lt;br/&gt;He was&#xA0;recently quoted for the Wall Street Journal article on Adult Orthodontics. &#x201C;Orthodontics combines health care with art,&#x201D; Kjeld says. &#x201C;Our patients&#x2019; faces are&#xA0;our canvases, and those smiles are showcased every day and have meaning for everything our patients do.&#x201D;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dr. Aamodt attended UCSF School of Dentistry, he completed a residency in the UCSF Division of Orthodontics.&#xA0;Dr. Aamodt has been involved in orthodontic research for several years,&#xA0;with a focus on understanding how the burden of malocclusion is distributed worldwide and how this has changed during the course of history, with a particular interest in why malocclusion develops. As a resident, Dr. Aamodt helped to build a network of universities in Central and South America to study how malocclusion and tooth decay may affect quality of life for indigenous groups.&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Kjeld Aamodt surfs and scuba dives, speaks Spanish, plays jazz guitar and bass, and recently got his private pilot&#x2019;s license. </description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object001.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty_Clinic/Entries/2016/2/3_Dr._Kjeld_Aamodt.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Sneha Oberoi</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty_Clinic/Entries/2016/2/3_Dr._Sneha_Oberoi.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a9df722-6e88-4590-8374-bdcb7079b352</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 3 Feb 2016 12:46:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Dr. Snehlata (Sneha) Oberoi, BDS, DDS, MDS, a board certified orthodontist, &#xA0;is the Director of the Cleft and Craniofacial Orthodontic Program and a Professor of Clinical Orofacial Sciences at the UCSF School of Dentistry. She completed her craniofacial orthodontic fellowship at UCSF in 2004, after receiving her dental and orthodontic training from India in 1994. She completed her certificate in Orthodontics from UCSF in 2014. She is the craniofacial orthodontist on the UCSF Craniofacial Team, where she provides assessment and treatment recommendations for children with cleft lip and palate and other craniofacial anomalies. She maintains a robust orthodontic faculty practice in the UCSF Orthodontic Clinic and is the attending for craniofacial patients treated by the residents. She provides teaching and supervision of orthodontic and pediatric dentistry residents and dental students on rotation in the Center for Craniofacial Anomalies. Dr. Oberoi has published over 50 articles in peer reviewed journals, as well as four book chapters. She serves as a reviewer for the Cleft Palate-Craniofacial Journal, the International Journal of Paediatric Dentistry, the Angle Orthodontist and the AJO-DO. Her research focuses on developing new methods to assess treatment outcomes for cleft lip and cleft palate and other craniofacial anomalies. She collaborates with the Center's medical geneticists to identify genetic mutations affecting orofacial defects. She lectures nationally and internationally. Dr. Oberoi is a member of the American Cleft Palate-Craniofacial Association, the American Association of Orthodontists, the Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists, California Association of Orthodontists and the Indian Orthodontic Society.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object007.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty_Clinic/Entries/2016/2/3_Dr._Sneha_Oberoi.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, MMMM d, y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Faculty_Clinic</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>5</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
