<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Current Events</title>
    <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events</link>
    <description>Contact Us for a Free Consultation
We provide high-quality Orthodontic Care including Clear Aligners like Invisalign.
To schedule your free consultation with a faculty member or resident, please call 415.476.2841. You may request a faculty member or resident when you call to schedule your appointment, depending on the type of provider you prefer.</description>
    <item>
      <title>Orthodontist Fellowship</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2016/7/29_Orthodontist_Fellowship.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66f6a352-100e-439f-ab44-5fc00c75c5e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 21:01:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>The Division of Orthodontics at the University of California, San Francisco is offering one-year fellowships to overseas-qualified orthodontists.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The program offers full participation in the didactic program and clinical experience in a modern orthodontic clinic working with our highly qualified faculty.  In addition, there will be opportunities for clinically oriented research.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All fellows are expected to conduct a research project and submit an article to a peer-reviewed journal during their tenure.  Upon completion of the program, the fellow will receive a &#x201C;Completion of Fellowship Certificate&#x201D; as documentation of their participation in the program. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In order to qualify for this opportunity, the fellow must have completed dental school and at least a two-year orthodontic program with a certificate of orthodontics in their home country.  The applicant must submit documentation to verify their orthodontic specialty training.  Applicants for the fellowship position must also submit at least two letters of recommendation from faculty in the orthodontic program from which they graduated. Furthermore, the fellow must have at least two years of practice experience either as faculty in a dental school&#x2019;s orthodontic program or in private practice.  A TOEFL test is required to ensure proficiency in the English language. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The fee for the one-year program is $ 55,000.  The applicants are responsible for their own living, housing and visa expenses related to the program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To apply, please contact: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:Melissa.Fung@ucsf.edu/"&gt;Melissa.Fung@ucsf.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Address:     707 Parnassus Avenue, D-3000&lt;br/&gt;                    San Francisco, California 94143-0438&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2016/7/29_Orthodontist_Fellowship.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preceptorship for Dentists</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2016/7/29_Preceptorship_for_Dentists.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90edcf78-5f3a-44fd-9969-e07006188df4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 08:25:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>The Division of Orthodontics at the University of California, San Francisco is offering a three months Preceptorship program in the specialty of Orthodontics to domestic and overseas-qualified dentists. The program is offered through the Continuing Education Program within the School of Dentistry at the University of California, San Francisco,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Division of Orthodontics at the University of California, San Francisco is offering a three months Preceptorship program in the specialty of Orthodontics to overseas-qualified dentists. The program is offered through the Continuing Education Program within the School of Dentistry at the University of California, San Francisco.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The goal of the Preceptorship is to provide educational experiences in the discipline of Orthodontics to trained professionals in the dental field. The program is designed to provide the visitor with an improved understanding of orthodontics and dentofacial orthopedics and an opportunity to improve his or her knowledge in one or more area of  complete the necessary paper work for enrollment. The orthodontic program will determine the optimal time for the visit and provide faculty resources and courses. &lt;br/&gt;The program offers full participation in the didactic program and clinical observation in a modern orthodontic clinic working with our highly qualified faculty.  In addition, there will be opportunities for limited research experience.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;All Preceptors are expected to conduct a limited research project during their tenure.  Upon completion of the program, the Preceptor will receive a &#x201C;Completion of Preceptorship Certificate&#x201D; as documentation of their participation in the program. &lt;br/&gt;In order to qualify for this opportunity, the candidate must have completed dental school from an accredited University in their home country, and have at least a two-years of either private practice experience or been on the faculty at a university program. &lt;br/&gt;The applicant must submit documentation to verify their dental education and also provide at least two letters of recommendation from faculty in the dental school from which they graduated.  A TOEFL test is required to ensure proficiency in the English language if an international applicant. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The fee for the three months program is $ 15,000.  The applicants are responsible for their own living, housing and visa expenses related to the program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To apply, please contact: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:Melissa.Fung@ucsf.edu/"&gt;Melissa.Fung@ucsf.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Address:     707 Parnassus Avenue, D-3000&lt;br/&gt;                    San Francisco, California 94143-0438&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2016/7/29_Preceptorship_for_Dentists.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fellowship in Craniofacial and Special Care Orthodontics</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2016/7/5_Fellowship_in_Craniofacial_Orthodontics.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a4718b1-2001-4976-a5e3-544ce81b0767</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 5 Jul 2016 13:31:52 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>The Division of Craniofacial Anomalies at the University of California, San Francisco is offering a one-year fellowship to qualified orthodontists.&lt;br/&gt;This is an ADA accredited post orthodontic residency fellowship program to provide advanced training and skills for the management of individuals with Craniofacial Anomalies and Special Care needs (CFA&amp;amp;SC), requiring complex multidisciplinary care. The focus of this subspecialty of orthodontics includes but is not limited to cleft lip and palate, syndromic craniosynostosis and other craniofacial anomalies, dentofacial deformities, craniofacial surgery, orthognathic surgery, distraction osteogenesis, nasoalveolar molding and special care orthodontics.&lt;br/&gt;The fellow will develop skills in the diagnosis and treatment planning using both two and three dimensional diagnostic record sets for complex craniofacial anomalies, requiring interdisciplinary team care. The fellow will be exposed to a large clinical population with congenital and acquired craniofacial abnormalities. The goal of the program is to train individuals to take an active role on a cleft and craniofacial treatment team and to be proficient in all growth and development and orthodontic management aspects.&lt;br/&gt;This Fellowship will provide the fellow with experience in the following clinical areas:&lt;br/&gt;1.	Newborn assessment for need of early intervention&lt;br/&gt;2.	Presurgical orthopedics (Nasoalveolar Molding) for infants born with cleft lip and palate if needed to align segments&lt;br/&gt;3.	Growth and orthodontic management from the primary through adult dentition and attainment of skeletal maturity.&lt;br/&gt;4.	Surgical/orthodontic treatment planning, pre- and post-surgical orthodontic management, surgical splint design and construction, and insertion of surgical fixation splints in the operating room.&lt;br/&gt;The fellow participates in weekly craniofacial and cleft conference with specialist in nursing, ENT, craniofacial surgery, speech, neurosurgery, genetics, prosthodontics, social work and psychology. Interdisciplinary treatment planning sessions are scheduled routinely to examine patients with the surgeons and other specialty team members as needed. The fellow will be expected to initiate and complete at least one clinical research project during the training. This will be mentored by craniofacial orthodontic or plastic surgery faculty members. The fellow is expected to present a research paper at national or international meeting during the Fellowship period.&lt;br/&gt;For additional information about the goals and content of the program, please contact:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Snehlata Oberoi,  DDS, MDS&lt;br/&gt;Director of the Cleft and Craniofacial Orthodontic Program&#x2028;Professor of Clinical OFS&lt;br/&gt;Center for Craniofacial Anomalies&#x2028;University of California San Francisco&#x2028;Phone: 415-476-1138&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:sneha.oberoi@ucsf.edu/"&gt;sneha.oberoi@ucsf.edu&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ADMISSIONS REQUIREMENTS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	DDS or DMD degree or equivalent&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	Completion of accredited orthodontics certificate program (at least two-years)&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	TOEFL (for those applicants whose native language is not English and who have not completed at least one year of US college/university level studies). The institution code is 4840.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;APPLICATION PROCEDURES&lt;br/&gt;Applicants must submit the following items directly to UCSF on or before June 30th:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	UCSF Application with supporting documentation to:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;University of California, San Francisco&#x2028;Dental Admissions Office&#x2028;513 Parnassus Avenue, S-630&#x2028;San Francisco, CA. 94143-0430&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	Personal Statement of Purpose&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	Curriculum Vitae&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	Official transcript(s) sent directly from the issuing institution from all college and universities attended.&#x2028;&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	Official transcript(s) from foreign universities and Canadian institutions where English was not the official language of instruction.  Please note: Xerox or notarized copies are not acceptable.&#x2028;&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	Official course-by-course evaluation from Educational Credential Evaluators, Inc or World Education Services for ALL foreign transcripts received outside of the US including Canadian school where English was not the official language of instruction.&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	Official TOEFL (Test of English as a Foreign Language) scores. Test is required for those applicants whose native language is not English and have not attended a US institution for at least one year.  The institution code is 4840.&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	Three letters of recommendation; at least two letters should be from faculty in the applicant&#x2019;s orthodontics program.&#x2028;&lt;br/&gt;&#x2022;	Postgraduate Application Fee Form with non-refundable $__ fee ($__ for international students, including Canadian citizens) to:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;UCSF Office of the Registrar&#x2028;P.O. Box 742908&#x2028;Los Angeles, CA. 90074-2908&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Do not send any transcripts, letters of recommendation, other documents or correspondence to this address&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;TUITION AND FEES&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For the latest information regarding tuition and fees, please check Student Financial Services/Registrar&#x2019;s website.  If accepted into the program, the fellow will be responsible for providing their own funding for the program costs and living/housing expenses.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The application information below will be combined with the UCSF application (DW)&lt;br/&gt;Application&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Name:  &lt;br/&gt;Correspondence Address:  &lt;br/&gt;Phone number:&lt;br/&gt;Email:  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Are you currently full-time/part time faculty or part of a craniofacial team?   Y      N&lt;br/&gt;If yes, which craniofacial team or university?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Work/Study VISA required?   Y    N&lt;br/&gt;US or Canadian trained-orthodontist ___     International orthodontist ___&lt;br/&gt;Dental School:                                                             dates: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Orthodontic residency:                                                dates:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Number of years: _________                 Number of patients treated in residency    ____&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;____Transcript or list of courses in orthodontics:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;____References&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;____Interests outside of orthodontics&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;____Can come for interview&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A.	 Please write a short 150 word essay on your goals of completing this training and plans after completion of the fellowship. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;B.	Please write a paragraph about craniofacial research interests.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2016/7/5_Fellowship_in_Craniofacial_Orthodontics.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>MMMM d, y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>3</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
