<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Current Events</title>
    <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events</link>
    <description>Contact Us for a Free Consultation
We provide high-quality Orthodontic Care including Clear Aligners like Invisalign.
To schedule your free consultation with a faculty member or resident, please call 415.476.2841. You may request a faculty member or resident when you call to schedule your appointment, depending on the type of provider you prefer.</description>
    <item>
      <title>Orthodontic Residency</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2015/12/20_Orthodontic_Residency.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62730697-7e26-4b1b-a8c2-fd7747cb47a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 12:31:15 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>MISSION&lt;br/&gt;The mission of the UCSF Postgraduate Program in Orthodontics is to contribute to the orthodontic specialty, orthodontic academic programs, orthodontic research, and the public by graduating broadly educated and well-trained clinician scientists.  An important ancillary mission of the educational process is to deliver quality orthodontic care for UCSF clinic patients.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PROGRAM DESCRIPTION &lt;br/&gt;This is a full time program, requiring 36 months in active residence beginning July 1 each year. It is designed to prepare future leaders in the specialty of orthodontics, qualified for academic careers as well as for clinical practice. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The program combines a foundation in basic sciences with clinical and behavioral training relevant to the delivery of orthodontic treatment.  Residents perform orthodontic care for the prevention and correction of malocclusions and facial disproportions.  The patient population includes children and adults. We emphasize a good knowledge base of maxillofacial structures and the function of the neuromuscular system.  The facility is modern.  Residents learn to operate a CBCT unit and to evaluate the scans. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Instruction includes lectures, seminars, demonstrations, laboratory experience and conferences.  These experiences are coordinate with the clinical treatment of patients. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Residents learn clinical skills while working in a team consisting of a first-, second-, and third-year resident and a full-time, highly skilled registered dental assistant.  Attending faculty is present for every patient visit. We teach orthodontic care with a variety of fixed and removable appliances.  All dental specialties are adjacent to the orthodontic clinic, facilitating interdisciplinary opportunities with oral and maxillofacial surgeons, periodontists, pediatric dentists, prosthodontists, and TMD specialists. Consultation with all medical specialists is also available on campus.  In the area of craniofacial anomalies, residents develop skills to evaluate the etiology, diagnosis, and prognosis of such patients.  Residents perform orthodontic treatment for patients with craniofacial anomalies and have a rotation in an active craniofacial diagnostic team. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The certificate program is combined with the postgraduate academic program in Oral and Craniofacial Sciences, leading to the M.S. degree within the 3-year residency.  Residents complete a research project under the supervision of a faculty mentor.  We also offer a combined PhD-certificate program, which can be selected for those residents who are interested in pursuing an academic career. There is support available for the PhD portion (3-5 years) from the Oral and Craniofacial Sciences Program. </description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object011.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2015/12/20_Orthodontic_Residency.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthodontist Fellowship</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2012/11/15_Prospective_International_Orthodontists.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66f6a352-100e-439f-ab44-5fc00c75c5e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:01:19 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>The Division of Orthodontics at the University of California, San Francisco is offering one-year fellowships to overseas-qualified orthodontists.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The program offers full participation in the didactic program and clinical experience in a modern orthodontic clinic working with our highly qualified faculty.  In addition, there will be opportunities for clinically oriented research.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All fellows are expected to conduct a research project and submit an article to a peer-reviewed journal during their tenure.  Upon completion of the program, the fellow will receive a &#x201C;Completion of Fellowship Certificate&#x201D; as documentation of their participation in the program. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In order to qualify for this opportunity, the fellow must have completed dental school and at least a two-year orthodontic program with a certificate of orthodontics in their home country.  The applicant must submit documentation to verify their orthodontic specialty training.  Applicants for the fellowship position must also submit at least two letters of recommendation from faculty in the orthodontic program from which they graduated. Furthermore, the fellow must have at least two years of practice experience either as faculty in a dental school&#x2019;s orthodontic program or in private practice.  A TOEFL test is required to ensure proficiency in the English language. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The fee for the one-year program is $ 55,000.  The applicants are responsible for their own living, housing and visa expenses related to the program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To apply, please contact: &lt;br/&gt;Ib Leth Nielsen, DDS, MSc&lt;br/&gt;Program Director - Post Graduate Orthodontics&lt;br/&gt;E mail: &lt;a href="mailto:ib.nielsen@ucsf.edu/"&gt;ib.nielsen@ucsf.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Address:     707 Parnassus Avenue, D-3000&lt;br/&gt;                    San Francisco, California 94143-0438&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2012/11/15_Prospective_International_Orthodontists.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preceptorship for Dentists</title>
      <link>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2012/11/15_International_Preceptorship_for_Dentists.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90edcf78-5f3a-44fd-9969-e07006188df4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 08:25:02 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>The Division of Orthodontics at the University of California, San Francisco is offering a three months Preceptorship program in the specialty of Orthodontics to domestic and overseas-qualified dentists. The program is offered through the Continuing Education Program within the School of Dentistry at the University of California, San Francisco,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Division of Orthodontics at the University of California, San Francisco is offering a three months Preceptorship program in the specialty of Orthodontics to overseas-qualified dentists. The program is offered through the Continuing Education Program within the School of Dentistry at the University of California, San Francisco.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The goal of the Preceptorship is to provide educational experiences in the discipline of Orthodontics to trained professionals in the dental field. The program is designed to provide the visitor with an improved understanding of orthodontics and dentofacial orthopedics and an opportunity to improve his or her knowledge in one or more area of  complete the necessary paper work for enrollment. The orthodontic program will determine the optimal time for the visit and provide faculty resources and courses. &lt;br/&gt;The program offers full participation in the didactic program and clinical observation in a modern orthodontic clinic working with our highly qualified faculty.  In addition, there will be opportunities for limited research experience.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Requirements:&lt;br/&gt;All Preceptors are expected to conduct a limited research project during their tenure.  Upon completion of the program, the Preceptor will receive a &#x201C;Completion of Preceptorship Certificate&#x201D; as documentation of their participation in the program. &lt;br/&gt;In order to qualify for this opportunity, the candidate must have completed dental school from an accredited University in their home country, and have at least a two-years of either private practice experience or been on the faculty at a university program. &lt;br/&gt;The applicant must submit documentation to verify their dental education and also provide at least two letters of recommendation from faculty in the dental school from which they graduated.  A TOEFL test is required to ensure proficiency in the English language if an international applicant. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The fee for the three months program is $ 15,000.  The applicants are responsible for their own living, housing and visa expenses related to the program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To apply, please contact: &lt;br/&gt;Ib Leth Nielsen, DDS, MSc&lt;br/&gt;Program Director - Post Graduate Orthodontics&lt;br/&gt;E mail: &lt;a href="mailto:ib.nielsen@ucsf.edu/"&gt;ib.nielsen@ucsf.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Address:     707 Parnassus Avenue, D-3000&lt;br/&gt;                    San Francisco, California 94143-0438&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events/Entries/2012/11/15_International_Preceptorship_for_Dentists.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>MMMM d, y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://carmelartist.com/ucsfortho/UCSF_Orthodontics/Current_Events</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>3</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
