<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="1E08F395-AD12-4A7E-93BD-F04EF0C6B859">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160729" date="2016-07-29 16:15:25 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;GLOBAL HEALTH&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Preceptorship for Dentists</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>The Division of Orthodontics at the University of California, San Francisco is offering a three months Preceptorship program in the specialty of Orthodontics to domestic and overseas-qualified dentists. The program is offered through the Continuing Education Program within the School of Dentistry at the University of California, San Francisco,&#xD;&#xD;The Division of Orthodontics at the University of California, San Francisco is offering a three months Preceptorship program in the specialty of Orthodontics to overseas-qualified dentists. The program is offered through the Continuing Education Program within the School of Dentistry at the University of California, San Francisco.&#xD;&#xD;The goal of the Preceptorship is to provide educational experiences in the discipline of Orthodontics to trained professionals in the dental field. The program is designed to provide the visitor with an improved understanding of orthodontics and dentofacial orthopedics and an opportunity to improve his or her knowledge in one or more area of  complete the necessary paper work for enrollment. The orthodontic program will determine the optimal time for the visit and provide faculty resources and courses. &#xD;The program offers full participation in the didactic program and clinical observation in a modern orthodontic clinic working with our highly qualified faculty.  In addition, there will be opportunities for limited research experience.&#xD;&#xD;Requirements:&#xD;All Preceptors are expected to conduct a limited research project during their tenure.  Upon completion of the program, the Preceptor will receive a &#x201C;Completion of Preceptorship Certificate&#x201D; as documentation of their participation in the program. &#xD;In order to qualify for this opportunity, the candidate must have completed dental school from an accredited University in their home country, and have at least a two-years of either private practice experience or been on the faculty at a university program. &#xD;The applicant must submit documentation to verify their dental education and also provide at least two letters of recommendation from faculty in the dental school from which they graduated.  A TOEFL test is required to ensure proficiency in the English language if an international applicant. &#xD;&#xD;The fee for the three months program is $ 15,000.  The applicants are responsible for their own living, housing and visa expenses related to the program.&#xD;&#xD;To apply, please contact: &#xD;&lt;a href="mailto:Melissa.Fung@ucsf.edu"&gt;Melissa.Fung@ucsf.edu&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;Address:     707 Parnassus Avenue, D-3000&#xD;                    San Francisco, California 94143-0438&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;July 29, 2016&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
