<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="1E08F395-AD12-4A7E-93BD-F04EF0C6B859">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160821" date="2016-08-21 22:17:29 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;GLOBAL HEALTH&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Fellowship in Craniofacial and Special Care Orthodontics</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>The Division of Craniofacial Anomalies at the University of California, San Francisco is offering a one-year fellowship to qualified orthodontists.&#xD;This is an ADA accredited post orthodontic residency fellowship program to provide advanced training and skills for the management of individuals with Craniofacial Anomalies and Special Care needs (CFA&amp;SC), requiring complex multidisciplinary care. The focus of this subspecialty of orthodontics includes but is not limited to cleft lip and palate, syndromic craniosynostosis and other craniofacial anomalies, dentofacial deformities, craniofacial surgery, orthognathic surgery, distraction osteogenesis, nasoalveolar molding and special care orthodontics.&#xD;The fellow will develop skills in the diagnosis and treatment planning using both two and three dimensional diagnostic record sets for complex craniofacial anomalies, requiring interdisciplinary team care. The fellow will be exposed to a large clinical population with congenital and acquired craniofacial abnormalities. The goal of the program is to train individuals to take an active role on a cleft and craniofacial treatment team and to be proficient in all growth and development and orthodontic management aspects.&#xD;This Fellowship will provide the fellow with experience in the following clinical areas:&#xD;1.	Newborn assessment for need of early intervention&#xD;2.	Presurgical orthopedics (Nasoalveolar Molding) for infants born with cleft lip and palate if needed to align segments&#xD;3.	Growth and orthodontic management from the primary through adult dentition and attainment of skeletal maturity.&#xD;4.	Surgical/orthodontic treatment planning, pre- and post-surgical orthodontic management, surgical splint design and construction, and insertion of surgical fixation splints in the operating room.&#xD;The fellow participates in weekly craniofacial and cleft conference with specialist in nursing, ENT, craniofacial surgery, speech, neurosurgery, genetics, prosthodontics, social work and psychology. Interdisciplinary treatment planning sessions are scheduled routinely to examine patients with the surgeons and other specialty team members as needed. The fellow will be expected to initiate and complete at least one clinical research project during the training. This will be mentored by craniofacial orthodontic or plastic surgery faculty members. The fellow is expected to present a research paper at national or international meeting during the Fellowship period.&#xD;For additional information about the goals and content of the program, please contact:&#xD;&#xD;Snehlata Oberoi,  DDS, MDS&#xD;Director of the Cleft and Craniofacial Orthodontic Program&#x2028;Professor of Clinical OFS&#xD;Center for Craniofacial Anomalies&#x2028;University of California San Francisco&#x2028;Phone: 415-476-1138&#xD;&lt;a href="mailto:sneha.oberoi@ucsf.edu"&gt;sneha.oberoi@ucsf.edu&lt;/a&gt; &#xD;&#xD;ADMISSIONS REQUIREMENTS&#xD;&#xD;&#x2022;	DDS or DMD degree or equivalent&#xD;&#x2022;	Completion of accredited orthodontics certificate program (at least two-years)&#xD;&#x2022;	TOEFL (for those applicants whose native language is not English and who have not completed at least one year of US college/university level studies). The institution code is 4840.&#xD;&#xD;APPLICATION PROCEDURES&#xD;Applicants must submit the following items directly to UCSF on or before June 30th:&#xD;&#xD;	&#x2022;	&lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/AD7A45FB-CACE-4F23-950A-4262D0F9CF9A"&gt;UCSF Application with supporting documentation&#xD;&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;University of California, San Francisco&#x2028;Dental Admissions Office&#x2028;513 Parnassus Avenue, S-630&#x2028;San Francisco, CA. 94143-0430&#xD;&#xD;UCSF Office of the Registrar&#x2028;P.O. Box 742908&#x2028;Los Angeles, CA. 90074-2908&#xD;&#xD;&lt;i&gt;Do not send any transcripts, letters of recommendation, other documents or correspondence to this address&#xD;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;TUITION AND FEES&#xD;&#xD;For the latest information regarding tuition and fees, please check Student Financial Services/Registrar&#x2019;s website.  If accepted into the program, the fellow will be responsible for providing their own funding for the program costs and living/housing expenses.  &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;July 5, 2016&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
