<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="C54094C5-A9FC-47DC-AEE3-E313D161772C">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160107" date="2016-01-07 23:22:41 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Dr. Sneha Oberoi&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Dr. Snehlata (Sneha) Oberoi, BDS, DDS, MDS, a board certified orthodontist, &#xA0;is the Director of the Cleft and Craniofacial Orthodontic Program and a Professor of Clinical Orofacial Sciences at the UCSF School of Dentistry. She completed her craniofacial orthodontic fellowship at UCSF in 2004, after receiving her dental and orthodontic training from India in 1994. She completed her certificate in Orthodontics from UCSF in 2014. She is the craniofacial orthodontist on the UCSF Craniofacial Team, where she provides assessment and treatment recommendations for children with cleft lip and palate and other craniofacial anomalies. She maintains a robust orthodontic faculty practice in the UCSF Orthodontic Clinic and is the attending for craniofacial patients treated by the residents. She provides teaching and supervision of orthodontic and pediatric dentistry residents and dental students on rotation in the Center for Craniofacial Anomalies. Dr. Oberoi has published over 50 articles in peer reviewed journals, as well as four book chapters. She serves as a reviewer for the Cleft Palate-Craniofacial Journal, the International Journal of Paediatric Dentistry, the Angle Orthodontist and the AJO-DO. Her research focuses on developing new methods to assess treatment outcomes for cleft lip and cleft palate and other craniofacial anomalies. She collaborates with the Center's medical geneticists to identify genetic mutations affecting orofacial defects. She lectures nationally and internationally. Dr. Oberoi is a member of the American Cleft Palate-Craniofacial Association, the American Association of Orthodontists, the Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists, California Association of Orthodontists and the Indian Orthodontic Society.&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;September 30, 2013&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="30_Dr._Sneha_Oberoi_files/shapeimage_4.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="215px" height="307px"/>
</content>
