<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="C54094C5-A9FC-47DC-AEE3-E313D161772C">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160203" date="2016-02-03 21:06:44 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Dr. Paul Kasrovi&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Dr. Paul Kasrovi completed his doctoral and postdoctoral education at UCSF, receiving both a specialty certificate in Orthodontics and a Master of Science degree in Oral Biology. Dr. Kasrovi is board certified by the American Board of Orthodontics. Before making a career change to dentistry, he had received a Bachelor of Science in Biomedical Engineering from USC and a Master of Science in Electrical Engineering from the University of Pennsylvania and worked as a systems engineer for AT&amp;T Bell Laboratories.&#xD;In addition to his commitment to the group practice, Dr. Kasrovi is a Clinical Professor at the UCSF School of Dentistry, division of Orthodontics where he has been teaching since 1995. He has also served as a Clinical Supervisor at the orthodontic teaching clinic at La Clinica de La Raza in Oakland.&#xD;As an active member of the orthodontic and dental community, Dr. Kasrovi is affiliated with several professional associations. His affiliations include:&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Presdent-Elect&#xA0;of the Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Past President and member of the California Association of Orthodontists&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Director and member of the Northern CA. Edward H. Angle Society of Orthodontists&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;University advocate for the American Board of Orthodontics&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Past President and member of the Berkeley Dental Society&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Member of the American Dental Association&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Member of the California Dental Association&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Member of the American Association of Orthodontists&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Member of the College of Diplomates of the American Board of Orthodontics&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Member of the Peninsula Orthodontic Research Group&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Member of Omicron Kappa Upsilon, a National Dental Honor Society&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dr. Kasrovi is a published author of articles in the American Journal of Orthodontics and Dentofacial Orthopedics, the Journal of the California Dental Association, and the Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists Bulletin. He has had his research presented at the meetings of the International Association of Dental Research&#xA0;and the American Society for Bone and Mineral Research. He has lectured on orthodontic care&#xA0;locally, nationally, and internationally.&#xD;Dr. Kasrovi and his wife, Leila, have two children, Dara and Kiana. Dr. Kasrovi enjoys spending time with his family and is passionate about traveling, skiing, soccer, Bay Area sports teams, and playing bass guitar in a local East Bay band.&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;November 30, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="30_Dr._Paul_Kasrovi_files/shapeimage_4.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="215px" height="307px"/>
</content>
